***
她愈來愈愛人類 渴望離開大海 來到人間
Wow, that was so bad, you guys.
你們唱得真爛
I think I threw up in my mouth a little.
我都有點吐了
We probably scared all of the fish away.
我們可能把魚都嚇跑了
I never catch anything anyway.
反正我也釣不到啥
What, two beautiful women don't rate?
怎麼 釣到倆美女還不夠嗎
You kidding me? Pretty thing like you,
開玩笑 像你這樣的美女
you're not even a keeper.
千載難逢
I should toss you in right now.
我現在就來蹂躪你
So I'm gonna get some more beer.
我去拿點啤酒
Okay.
好
That's good.
太好了
Oh. Ooh, boy.
天吶
Oh, what do you want?
啥事啊
No, no, no, no.
不 不 不
You little pervert!
你這個小變態
What do you think you're doing?
你在幹嘛
You were not just walking around.
你才不是出來走走呢
I saw you spying on us. I'm gonna tell dad.
我看到你偷窺我們 我要告訴爸爸
no
不
you can't
不要
If you don't want me to tell him,
如果你不想我告訴他
you need to get your butt outta here.
那你就快滾
not him
別跟他在一起
anybody***
除了他 你跟誰都行
What do you care about Jake?
你喜歡Jake什麼
I mean, he doesn't even know that you exist.
他都不知道你的存在
i love him
我愛他
Look, you're never going to be the same as them, you know,
你永遠不能像他們那樣的
so you need to stop trying to become
所以你別再癡心妄想了 走吧
What, no beer?
怎麼 沒啤酒了
Changed my mind.
我改主意了
What's the matter? You scared of me?
怎麼了 你怕我啊
That was incredible.
真不可思議
You're incredible.
你太棒了
You're not so bad yourself.
你也不賴嘛
No!
不
No! Help! Help!
不 救命啊 救命
- Get out of the water! - What's going on?
- 快上岸 - 怎麼回事
Get out!
快上岸
Help!
救命
Dan! Dan!
Dan
-=伊甸园美剧http://bbs.sfile2012.com=- -=伊甸园字幕站 http://ytet.org=- 荣誉出品 本字幕仅供学习交流 严禁用于商业途径
-=伊甸園美劇http://bbs.sfile2012.com=- -=伊甸園字幕站 http://ytet.org=- 榮譽出品 本字幕僅供學習交流 嚴禁用於商業途徑
-=YTET-伊甸园民间字幕联盟=- 翻译: 校对:Achilles之踵 时间轴:wilson0804@A7
-=YTET-伊甸園民間字幕聯盟=- 翻譯:金萬藏 Hannah 玄武門饞貓小愛 滕秀星 校對:Achilles之踵 時間軸:wilson0804@A7
格林 第三季 第四集
格林 第三季 第四集
Dan.
Dan
Are you sure this is a good idea?
你確定這樣好嗎
Whoa, wait, what?
等等 什麼
Of course this is a good idea. This is a great idea,
當然 再好不過了
- 'cause you and I... - No, no.
- 因為你和我... - 不
- What? - Not that.
- 怎麼 - 不是說那事
I'm just... I'm saying I-I have so much stuff,
我是說 我東西好多
and your house suddenly seems a lot smaller.
你的房子忽然顯得小了好多
No, there's plenty of room. Plus, look.
不 空間多著呢 再說 你看
It's a golden opportunity for me to get rid of some stuff.
對我來說 這是除舊的良機
What are you going to get rid of?
你要扔掉什麼
Oh, you kidding? Any number of... like...
開玩笑 那麼多的...
or...
或者...
you know, like this, for example.
比如這個
Well, that's a start.
這也算個開頭吧
This was presented personally to my great, great Uncle Bernard
這是Sigmund Riefler親自送給
by Sigmund Riefler himself when Bernard retired
我曾叔公Bernard的 那時他剛從
from the clemens Riefler clock works in Munich.
慕尼黑的利夫勒鐘錶廠退休
Sigmund was the son of the founder clemens Riefler,
Sigmund是該廠創建人的兒子
but it was actually Sigmund who invented the Riefler escapement,
但其實是他發明了利夫勒擒縱棘輪
which is a mechanical device for precision pendulum clocks.
那是用於精密擺鐘的機械裝置
And I actually have one right over there.
我還真有一個 就在那邊
So...
那麼...
I think everything should stay right where it is.
我想這些東西還是放著好了
Even me.
包括我
I cut up some fruit. You want some?
我切了點水果 要吃點嗎
Yeah, please, and a lot of coffee.
好的 再來多點咖啡
Got you covered.
我早弄好了
What?
怎麼
Nothing.
沒什麼
That's what makes this so great.
這樣真好
Yeah, I really missed all this, like, everyday stuff.
是啊 我真想念這樣的時光
I missed that too.
還有親吻
See you after work.
下班後見
Hey, hey, what about the doctor's reports?
醫生報告怎麼說
Oh, he was supposed to send me the email yesterday.
他昨天應該發我郵箱了
Just check my email, see if it came in.
看我的郵箱裡有沒有
Tell me if I'm still alive.
看看我還堅挺著
Gillnetter out on government island
今早島上的漁民
fished him out of the river this morning.
從河裡撈出了死者
I cross-checked with missing persons.
我比對檢查了失蹤人口
A report was filed yesterday matching his description,
昨日一宗報案的描述與死者相符
name listed as Daniel Hopkins.
他叫Daniel Hopkins
Same as we got.
跟我們收到的一樣
Report also lists as a possible assault.
報案還稱可能是襲擊案
Looks pretty beat up.
被揍得好慘
Probably from river debris.
可能被暗礁弄傷的
I don't know about these marks on his ankles.
他腳踝上的傷痕可不像是
Yeah, same here too, like scratches.
是啊 這也有 像是抓痕
Yeah, scratches or claws.
是的 爪子抓傷的
Maybe something pulled him under.
也許他是被什麼東西拉下水的
What are we talking, a loch ness monster?
說什麼呢 尼斯湖水怪嗎
- Who filed the report? - Uh, Jake Barnes.
- 誰報的案 - Jake Barnes
Filed last night at 9:15.
昨晚9點15分報案的
Let's talk to him.
我們去跟他談談
One second.
稍等
- Jake Barnes? - Yeah.
- Jake Barnes - 是的
I'm Detective Burkhardt. This is Detective Griffin.
我是Burkhardt警探 這位是Griffin警探
You filed a missing persons report for Daniel Hopkins.
你報案稱Daniel Hopkins失蹤了
Oh, God, did you find him?
天吶 你們找到他了
Mind if we talk inside?
能進去談嗎
Yeah, sure.
當然
So did he make it out?
他還活著嗎
Afraid not, they discovered Dan's body this morning.
抱歉 他們今早發現了Dan的屍體
Oh, man.
天啊
Oh, man, I was afraid of this.
天啊 我就怕這事
You know, he was... he was pulled underwater.
他被水底的東西拉下去的
By what?
被什麼拉的
I don't know, I just saw something, it got me too.
我不知道 我隱約看到 它也抓住了我
All right, we're gonna need you to go over
好吧 我們需要你回憶
everything that happened yesterday...
昨天發生的一切
where you were, who was there, anything you can remember.
去了哪 有誰在場 你能想起的一切
Oh, jeez.
天啊
He's really dead, I can't believe this.
他真的死了 我不敢相信
All right, was anyone else there with you?
還有誰跟你們在一起
No, not at first.
不 一開始沒有的
We were fishing up near steelhead,
我們本來在釣魚
and... and then these two girls showed up.
然後來了兩個女孩
- You get their names? - Mm-hmm.
你知道她們的名字嗎
Sarah and Anna.
Sarah和Anna
They were sisters, I didn't...
她們是姐妹
I'm sorry, I didn't get their last name.
抱歉 我不知道她們姓什麼
You must have got a number, right?
你有她們的電話號碼吧
I never had a chance.
我都沒機會要
I mean, one thing led to another.
事情就那樣發生了
Did things get sexual?
發生性關係了嗎
Yeah.
是的
Who were you with?
你跟誰一起
Sarah. Dan was with Anna.
我和Sarah Dan和Anna
We were all in the river. Sarah and I...
我們都在河裡 Sarah和我...
Anyway, afterwards, we were swimming, and...
後來我們在游泳
that's when I heard Dan.
我就聽到Dan的聲音
He was screaming, and Anna looked really scared,
他喊了起來 Anna很害怕
and she was yelling for us to get out of the river,
她大叫著我們快上岸
and... And then something...
然後有東西
something pulled him under.
有東西把他拉下水面了
Did you try to get to him?
你試著救他了嗎
Of course, but...
當然 但...
I mean, and then something pulled me under too.
有東西也拉我下水了
And then that's the last thing I remember.
那是我記得的最後一件事
Look, I told all this to the police last night.
我昨天已經把事情都跟警察說了
I don't think they believed me.
我想他們不相信我
How'd you manage to get out?
你怎麼逃出來的
I'm not sure.
我也不確定
I mean, all I know is there was this...
我只知道...
This what?
什麼事
Girl, I think, but you know,
應該是個女孩吧
I mean, I'm not even sure she was real, man.
但我都不確定是不是自己幻覺
I mean, I was still just trying to breathe.
我還在掙扎
It wasn't Sarah or Anna?
不是Sarah或者Anna
No, this one was younger,
不 這個女孩更年輕一些
but I don't know, man, I don't know what I saw.
但我不知道看到了什麼
How'd you get those scratches?
你的抓痕是怎麼來的
I'm telling you, I mean, it felt like something,
我告訴你 感覺像是有東西
like, grabbed me.
抓住了我
Okay, what kind of something?
那是什麼東西
I mean, it's a little hard to focus when you're drowning.
溺水時很難注意
Why don't you take us to the place
不如你帶我們去案發現場吧
My car was parked behind these trees.
我的車停在那些樹的後面
We came down here and made a campfire.
我們到這邊來 生了一堆篝火
My clothes were right here, Dan's too.
我的衣服在這裡 Dan的也是
I mean, I looked all up and down the river for him.
我沿著河邊找過他
I should have gone in after him, but after what happened...
我本該下水找他的 但有過溺水的經歷後...
Is this where you went into the river?
你是從這裡下水的
Yes.
是的
And where'd you get pulled out?
你從哪裡被拉上來
Down there, I guess.
我想是那邊吧
What happened to the girls you were with?
和你們在一起的女孩呢
I don't know, I...
不知道
I mean, I thought maybe they got grabbed too,
我以為她們也被抓住了
but then their clothes were gone when I came to.
但我上來時 她們的衣服已經不見了
You said there was another girl that pulled you out.
你說另有一個女孩把你拉上來
What happened to her?
她人呢
Uh, I think she ran off
她把我從河裡拉上來後就跑掉了
Now, when'd you call 911?
你什麼時候報警的
Soon as I got back up here.
我一上來就打了
I couldn't find my phone, so I used Dan's.
但沒找到我的手機 我用了Dan的
How'd the girls get here?
女孩子們怎麼到這來的
Uh, just from back there.
就從後面出來了
- You didn't see a car? - No.
- 你沒看見有車 - 沒
Hank!
Hank
Police!
警察
Stop!
站住
I'm not gonna hurt you!
我不會傷害你
What happened?
怎麼了
She dove in.
她潛到水裡了
- You see her come up? - Yeah, about 50 yards out.
- 你看見她露頭了 - 近乎50米之外
She swam all that way underwater?
她潛游了那麼遠
What are we dealing with?
我們這次遇到的是什麼
Hey, hey, I think that's the girl I saw when I came up.
那好像就是我上岸時看見的女孩
- Where'd she go? - I'm not sure.
- 她去哪了 - 不知道
River patrol didn't find any bodies
河岸巡邏隊沒發現任何屍體
matching Jake's description of Sarah, Anna,
符合Jake描述的Sarah或Anna
or the girl Nick saw jump into the river.
也沒有符合Nick所見 跳進河裡的女孩
They're probably still alive. Somebody went back
她們可能還活著 有人回到
to the campsite and took the sisters' clothes.
營地拿走了那對姐妹的衣服
Jake said they were scared.
Jake說她們嚇壞了
They probably got out of the river,
她們很可能一上岸
grabbed their stuff, and ran.
抓起衣服就跑了
The girl I saw go into the river
我看見那跳進河裡的女孩
was a lot more than a girl when she got under the water.
可不像普通人
- You know what she was? - Not yet.
- 你知道她是什麼嗎 - 還不知道
Let's round up the unusual suspects.
去查查這些不尋常的嫌犯吧
Oui?
喂
***
你一個人嗎
Adalind.
Adalind
In the river?
在河裡
You know, I'm not really that much of a water person.
我可不是喜歡撲騰水的人
I'm really more of a Mountain and land kind of lubber.
我更是那種跑山穿林的野漢子
There was this girl I knew in Seattle, she was a naiad,
我在西雅圖見過一個女孩 她是水精
lived out on Bainbridge island.
在班布裡奇島上生活
She's was kind of weird,
她是有點古怪
nice, though.
但是個好人
But she could swim, man, like a fish.
她游泳特別厲害 簡直像一條魚
Uh, naiad?
水精
Oh, naiads. Yeah, no, I've heard of naiads.
水精 我聽說過
I've never seen one, though.
但從來沒見過
What are they, like, a water nymph or something?
像是水中仙女嗎
Sort of. Very close-knit families.
有點 可以說非常相似
They never stray far from the water.
他們從來不遠離水域
That's probably why Jake can't describe who saved him.
難怪Jake無法描述是誰救了他
I bet you'd have something about them in your trailer.
你的拖車裡肯定有相關記載
Well, at least we have an idea of what we're dealing with now.
現在至少知道了對手的身份
Yeah.
是啊
Right, we should be going.
我們也該走了
Looks like you guys have a lot left to do.
看來你們有的可忙了
Yeah, we do. We sure do.
那是
Hey, you know, but if you guys need any help,
如果你們需要幫助
you know, in the trailer...
去拖車裡找資料
I mean, I probably shouldn't leave with so much left to do.
我留下一大堆活 恐怕不太好
- Go ahead. - Are you sure?
- 去吧 - 你確定
I mean, it's not gonna take that long.
我應該不會去很久
Please, take him.
帶上他吧
Thanks.
多謝
Oh, listen to this, it's dated 1755.
聽聽這個 在1755年
Looks like a Grimm working for the East India company.
有個格林為東印度公司工作過
"A strange event aboard the merchant vessel Doddington.
多丁頓號商船上 發生了件怪事
"Jory, our third mate, disappeared overnight.
三副Jory一夜之間消失了
"The rest of the crew grows superstitious.
其它船員日漸迷信
"Recently, Jory had taken to raving
近來Jory總是滔滔不絕
"about a beautiful woman
有個美女
"swimming alongside our ship like a fish.
像魚一樣伴著商船游來游去
"I have decided to stand the man's watch
等我們繞過海峽時
"as we round the cape
我決定好好查探
"to see if there is any truth to these rumors.
看看是否確有其事
"It turns out Jory was no lunatic.
結果 Jory沒有胡說
"I saw the creature known to my kin as the naiad.
我看見我們稱之為水精的生物
"After capturing it in a net,
我網住了一隻
"I was able to haul the creature aboard,
把她拖到甲板上
"where she donned her human shape.
她變成了人類的形態
"I find her mesmerizing
我發現她極具魅惑性
"and have kept her hidden from the Captain and crew.
就背著船長和船員藏起了她
"After some hours on board,
在船上呆幾個小時後
"the woman's skin began to dry and peel.
她的皮膚開始乾燥剝落
"She begs me to return her to the sea,
她求我把她放回大海
"but I am determined to prove Jory true.
但我決定要還Jory個清白
"I have questioned her regarding his disappearance,
我問她Jory的下落
"but she refuses to betray any secrets of her kind
但她不願背叛同類
and only pleads to be let back into the water."
只是乞求著要回到水裡
"At sunrise this morning, the creature died
次日太陽升起 她死了
"from what I assume was severe dehydration.
我想是因為極度脫水
"I'm afraid whatever secrets the naiad was keeping
不管水精有什麼秘密
have died with her."
都隨她一起消失了
It's wu.
是Wu打來的
Got something for us?
找到什麼線索了嗎
We ran the number
查了一下
from Jake Barnes' missing cell phone.
Jake Barnes所丟電話的號碼
GPS puts it at the andersen marina.
GPS顯示電話在安徒生碼頭
That's not far up the river
離他們游泳的河流不遠
How you want to handle this?
想怎麼處理
Meet us at the marina.
我們碼頭見
We should bring Jake along
把Jake也帶去
in case he can I.D. whoever took the phone.
或許他能認出拿走他的電話的人
- You ever been here? - No.
- 你來過這嗎 - 沒有
You know anybody who lives here?
你認識的人有誰住在這嗎
Not that I know of.
也沒有
- Stay in the car. - See if you recognize anybody.
呆在車裡 看你能不能認出誰來
The phone's still on... In one of these houseboats.
手機還開著 就在其中一戶船屋裡
Looks like this one here.
應該是這座
Sir, I'm Detective Burkhardt. This is Detective Griffin.
先生 我是Burkhardt警探 這是Griffin警探
We're following up an investigation about a drowning.
我們在調查一個溺水案
Need to ask you a few questions. Who drowned?
- 需要問你幾個問題 - 誰溺水了
Can I have your name, sir?
請問你的名字 先生
Abel Mahario.
Abel Mahario
I don't know anybody who drowned.
我不知道有什麼人溺水了
We're tracking a stolen cell phone.
我們追蹤一個被盜手機
It was taken from where the victim went into the river.
是在受害者遇難的河邊被盜的
The signal led us here. Mind if we take a look inside?
- 我們跟蹤手機信號來到這 - 能讓我們進去看一下嗎
I haven't done anything wrong, and I told you
我可什麼都沒做
I don't know anybody who drowned,
我也不知道有誰溺水了
so this must be a mistake.
肯定是什麼地方弄錯了
Should be easy enough to find out.
有個簡單的辦法可以驗證
Calling the stolen cell phone now.
給被盜手機打個電話
That sounds like probable cause to me.
這就是我們的爭當理由
We're going inside, sir.
我們要進去看看 先生
Sir, will you stay right here?
先生 請你不要動
So how'd Jake's phone get in here?
Jake的手機怎麼跑到這來了
Girl on the left looks like the one I chased into the river.
左邊的女孩像是我追到河裡的那個
- The naiad? - Let's find out.
- 水精 - 去證實一下吧
Sir, do you want to take a crack
先生 請你說一下
at how this cell phone got in your house?
這手機怎麼跑到你房子裡了
I have no idea how it got there.
我一點都不知道
This girl, is she your daughter?
這個女孩 是你的女兒嗎
Why? Elly didn't do anything.
怎麼了 Elly什麼都沒做
She may have been in the area at the time of the drowning.
發生溺水事件時 她可能就在附近
We need talk to her, see if she saw anything.
我們要和她談談 看她是否看見了什麼
Well, you can't talk to her.
你們可沒法和她談
Sir, this is a police investigation.
先生 這是警方調查
She's deaf, so unless one of you can sign...
她是聾子 除非你們誰會手語
Hey, Sarah. Sarah.
Sarah
Sarah, hey. Yeah, it's me, Jake.
Sarah 是我 Jake
Hey, hey, hey. Whoa, guys.
喂喂 姑娘們
Guys, guys, wait. Whoa, hold on.
二位 二位 等一下
Look, they found Dan's body.
他們發現了Dan的屍體
I don't know what you're talking about.
我不知道你在說什麼
Dan, he drowned. The police are here.
Dan 他溺水了 警察都來了
- We have to go. - Wait, I'm sorry,
- 我們要走了 - 等一下 不好意思
did you hear what I just said? Dan's dead!
你們聽到我說的了嗎 Dan死了
Why don't you just leave us alone?
請你別來打擾我們好嗎
Guys, these are the girls I was telling you about.
這就是我對你們說的那兩個女孩
Sarah and Anna. Sarah, Anna, get in the house.
- Sarah和Anna - Sarah Anna 進屋
Everyone's gonna stay right here
所有人先都別動
until we're done questioning them.
我們要一一詢問
- Who was with Dan? - Anna.
- 當時誰和Dan在一起 - Anna
I was swimming with Sarah.
我當時在和Sarah游泳
I don't know what he's talking about.
我不知道他在說什麼
What, are you crazy?
什麼 你瘋了麼
Look, we were together yesterday.
我們昨天一起玩來著
All right, we're gonna need to see some identification.
好吧 我要看看你們的身份證
My girls didn't do anything wrong.
我女兒沒做錯什麼
I.Ds. Now, you wanna tell us
身份證 那你想說說你們
where you were yesterday afternoon and evening?
昨天下午和晚上都做什麼了
- We were here with our dad. - They were with me and Dan.
- 我們和爸爸在一起 - 她們跟我和Dan在一起
Anna?
Anna
Hey, what the hell's going on here?
嘿 到底什麼事
It's a police investigation, sir.
是警方調查 先生
I need you to stop right there.
我需要你停在那兒
Investigation of what?
調查什麼
- Who are you? - We live over there.
- 你們是誰 - 我們住那邊
Then I suggest you go home and stay out of it,
我建議你們回自己家 別管閒事
unless you want my sergeant to put you in the back of his car.
除非你想被關警車裡
I already told you, my girls were home last night.
我已經說了 昨晚我女兒們一直在家
You recognize this girl?
你認識這個女孩
Yeah, I mean, that looks like the girl who saved me.
是啊 長得像救我的女孩
You want to explain how this cell phone got in your house?
能解釋下這手機怎麼在你家嗎
That's my phone. They had my phone?
那是我的手機 她們拿了我的手機
Fine, you don't want to explain here, I get it.
好吧 你們不想解釋 我明白了
Sarah, Anna, you go back to the precinct with us.
Sarah Anna 你們跟我們回分局
Let's go. This way, please.
走吧 請這邊走
Anyone else want to go?
還有人想來嗎
Let's get back in the car.
回車裡吧
Listen, you can't do this.
你們不能這樣做
Sir, we can make the same arrangements for you,
先生 我們也可以把你帶回去
unless you want to clear this up right now.
除非你現在給我個解釋
You don't understand.
你不明白
Well, I guess we have more to talk about than I thought.
看來我們可以聊的還挺多
But I'm going to talk to your daughters first,
但我會先跟你女兒談
give you some time to think about it.
給你點時間考慮
Damn it.
該死
I told you I didn't want this kind of trouble.
我跟你們說了我不想要這種麻煩
Why did you do it?
你們為什麼要這麼做
Because you forgot where you come from. We haven't.
因為你忘了你的出身 我們還沒
I haven't forgotten anything.
我什麼都沒忘
I know what it takes for us to survive.
我知道生存的條件
Your world died 200 years ago,
你們的世界200年前就消亡了
and now you've jeopardized all of us
現在你用這無稽之談
with this fundamental crap!
陷我們於危險之中
It was Elly, your daughter.
是Elly 你女兒
She pulled him out.
她把他拉出來的
Which is how that phone got in your house.
所以他的手機在你家裡
She has to be cut.
得割了她
Are you crazy? Nobody does that anymore.
你瘋了嗎 沒人這麼做了
Where we're from, they do,
我們的故鄉 就這樣做
and we don't have these kinds of troubles.
我們可沒這些麻煩
And this is your fault, old man.
這是你的錯 大叔
This is what happens when you don't raise your women right.
你不好好教育你的女兒 就會發生這樣的事
No, no, wait.
不 不 等等
Please, she's just a girl.
別這樣 她只是個女孩
I'm not gonna let you touch her.
我不會讓你們碰她的
Who's gonna stop us?
來攔住我們啊
Jake says this is the girl that pulled him out.
Jake說這是救他的女孩
You want to tell us what happened?
能說說事情經過嗎
We're the only two here
這裡只有我們知道
who know what you and your sister are.
你和你姐姐是什麼
I don't know what you're talking about.
我不知道你在說什麼
You're naiads.
你們是水精
You really want to spend the next 24 hours
接下來的24小時你真的想
drying out in a holding cell? 'Cause that's where
- 在拘留室裡脫水 - 你若不開始交代
you're going if you don't start talking.
你就得進去
I have nothing to say.
我沒什麼可說的
Well, let's hope your sister does.
願你姐姐會說吧
Jake saw Dan pulled under.
Jake看到Dan被拉到水底去
Jake is only alive because Elly saved him.
Jake還活著 因為Elly救了他
That means you either saw what happened
說明你要麼看到事情經過
or were involved with what happened.
要麼就牽涉其中
You need to tell us, Anna.
你得告訴我們 Anna
Because I know naiads can only be out of the water for so long.
因為我知道水精 離開水只能活多久
And you will die in here if you don't start talking.
如果不開始交代 你會死在這兒
Who pulled Jake under the water?
誰把Jake拉下水底的
Who killed Dan?
誰殺了Dan
Knowing what they are and what will happen to them,
我們知道她們是什麼 會有何下場
we don't want to keep them locked up.
所以並不想拘留她們
But they're not giving us much choice.
但是她們沒給我們選擇餘地
At the very least, they know what happened
至少她們知道事情經過
and didn't report it. So they might know who did it.
- 但拒不交代 - 所以她們應該知道是誰幹的
That's the problem, we think they're protecting somebody.
問題就在這裡 我們覺得她們在保護某人
How much time do you think they have?
你覺得她們還能熬多久
I doubt they'll survive the night.
我懷疑撐不過今晚
And what about the girl who saved your victim
那個從河裡救起受害者的女孩呢
from the river? Can't find her.
找不到她
So how do we explain two dead women in our holding cells?
那我們要怎麼解釋拘留室裡 有兩個女孩死掉
We can't very well say they're naiads.
總不能說她們是水精吧
We'll get blamed for something we had no control over.
我們會因此擔責的
And they're playing a very serious game.
她們可是寧死不屈
If they're involved, what do we do, just let 'em go?
萬一她們是涉案人員 那要怎麼辦 放她們走嗎
No. This is their problem, not ours.
不 這是她們的問題 不是我們的
If they choose to die, we let the M.E. explain it.
如果她們選擇死 讓驗屍官解釋好了
Just 'cause they're wesen, it doesn't entitle them
不能因為他們是偽森
to special treatment.
就給他們特殊對待
Yeah?
什麼事
Girls' father, Abel Mahario, is here.
女孩的爸爸 Abel Mahario來了
Apparently, he wants to talk.
很明顯 他想開口了
I killed that boy. I did it.
我殺了那個男孩 是我做的
You need to arrest me and let my daughters go.
你得逮捕我 放了我女兒
- How'd you kill him? - I drowned him.
- 你怎麼殺他的 - 我淹死他的
Why?
為什麼
I have my reasons.
我有我的理由
I know you didn't do it for a cell phone.
我知道你不會因為一個手機這麼做
We know you want to save your girls,
我們知道你想救女兒
but we'd rather leave here with whoever's really responsible.
但我們更願意留下真正的嫌疑人
I am! I told you I did it!
我說了是我做的
I-I pulled him underwater!
我把他拉到水底的
- Were your daughters there too? - No.
- 你女兒也在場嗎 - 沒有
- Jake Barnes says they were. - Well, he's lying.
- Jake Barnes說他們在那兒 - 他在說謊
Why would he lie?
他為什麼要說謊
He just saw them.
他只是看到她們了
Then they were there?
那她們的確在場
I saw those two boys attacking my daughters,
我看到那兩個男孩襲擊我女兒
and I did what I had to.
我逼不得已動手
So you're telling us you were saving your daughters?
所以你是說 你在救女兒
They were being raped.
他們在強姦我女兒
Then why did your other daughter
那為什麼你另外的女兒
pull Jake out of the water?
把Jake拉出水
Who gave you the black eye?
誰把你打成熊貓眼
Did you know she was there too?
你知道她也在那兒嗎
What time did you get there?
你什麼時候到那裡的
- How did you get there? - You walk? Take a car?
- 你怎麼去的 - 走去的 開車去的
What did the other guy look like, the one you killed?
你殺的那男孩長什麼樣
Was he tall, short, fat, black, white?
高矮胖瘦 皮膚是黑是白
We need some details here.
我們需要點細節
Why don't you take us to the place where it happened?
你把我們帶到案發現場吧
You see how difficult this gets
你知道如果你不說真話
when you're not telling the truth?
有多難圓謊了吧
Why does it matter?
這很重要麼
I'm offering my life for my daughters'.
我拿我的命來換我女兒的
Not easy being a parent.
做父母真不易啊
Yeah, but it could be what we need.
但可能正是我們需要的
Those girls may be ready to throw their own lives away,
這些女孩可能已經把生命置之度外
but they might not be so willing when it's their dad's life
但如果是她們爸爸的命
they're dealing with.
可能就不願意了
Use his confession as leverage?
用他做籌碼
Might be just as tough being a daughter.
做個女兒可能也挺不容易的
I guess we'll find out if it's a loving family.
由此能看出家庭是否團結
You're the one who saved my life.
是你救了我的命
What's your name?
你叫什麼名字
Elly.
Elly
Okay.
好吧
What are you doing here, Elly?
你在這兒幹嗎 Elly
Oh, you're deaf?
哦 你聽不到
But you can read my lips?
但是你會讀唇語
Okay.
好吧
Wow.
哇哦
You know, I almost thought I imagined you.
我差點以為你是我想像出來的
Um, the police need to talk to you.
警察要找你談話
The police, they're looking for you.
警察在找你
What are you doing?
你要幹嘛
You want to show me something?
你想給我看什麼
Something about you? Okay.
關於你的事情 好吧
What are you doing?
你想幹嘛
You want to go swimming?
你想游泳
Huh? Now?
現在
Elly.
Elly
Oh, my God.
天啊
You... you're what I saw.
我沒看錯吧
My God, you're real?
天啊 你是真的
No!
不
No! No!
不 不
Hey! What's going on down there?
嘿 下面在幹嘛
- Mm! - We gotta go.
我們得走了
The last in a long line of boxes.
眾多箱子裡的最後一個
What have we here?
有什麼呢
- Oh, I'm not sure. - Whoa.
我也不太清楚
That was in my brother's apartment.
那是我哥哥公寓裡的
This is really...
這真是...
It-it's interesting. Oh, wow!
真是 有意思
I have not seen that since I was a kid.
長大後就沒見過它了
Belonged to my grandparents.
我祖父母的
They brought it with them from Holland.
他們從荷蘭帶來的
Well, in that case, it should sit in a place of honor.
這樣一來 得給它排個好位置
Hey. Don't try so hard.
別太難為你自己了
I know this is a big deal for you and me,
同居對咱倆都是大事
moving in together, but we have to be honest.
但我們得坦誠相待
That is butt ugly.
這東西醜死了
- I know, but... - But what?
- 我懂 但是 - 但是啥
I mean, maybe there's things of mine that you don't like.
或許我的一些事會惹你煩
What are you afraid of?
你在擔心什麼
Me.
我
Why?
為啥
There have been other... you know,
我也談過幾個...
but no one I ever even considered moving in with.
但從未想過要跟誰同居
Are you getting cold feet?
你有些退縮了吧
No. God, no. I knew it would sound like that.
不 絕對不是 我就知道你會這麼想
Stop.
打住
It's okay. It's all going to be okay.
沒事 一切都會好的
I just didn't want you to think...
我就是不想讓你覺得...
- stop thinking. - Mm.
別瞎想了
I love you, you love me,
我愛你 你也愛我
and we both hate this.
咱倆都不喜歡這個
And if you can't build a relationship on hate...
若連自己不喜歡啥都不能說
Right, then... I mean, what do you have?
對 那還能有什麼
Us.
彼此
Your father confessed to everything.
你們的父親全招了
You are free to go. What?
- 你倆可以走了 - 什麼
What did... what did he confess to?
他招了什麼
The murder of Dan Hopkins
他殺了Dan Hopkins
and the attempted murder of Jake Barnes.
並企圖謀殺Jake Barnes
- That's a lie. - You think we'd be
- 他沒說真話 - 你倆肯定以為
letting you go if we didn't have a confession?
沒人認罪也能被放走是吧
No. This isn't right.
不 這樣不好
Sarah, they're letting us go.
Sarah 他們放我們走了
And arresting dad? He'll die here.
把爸爸關進來 他會死在這兒的
We can talk about this at home.
這個我們可以回家再商量
It's dad, Anna.
這可是咱爸啊 Anna
Sarah, don't.
Sarah 不要
Dominic did it.
Dominic干的
- Dominic? - And Jesse too.
- Dominic - 和Jesse
It's those two guys from the marina.
是住碼頭上的那倆人幹的
They'll kill us, Sarah.
他們會殺了我們
You don't have much time left. We need to get you out of here.
你們時間不多了 我們得放你們離開
Sarah, he's a Grimm. You can't trust him.
他是格林 不要相信他
I have no choice.
我別無他選
Let's go.
我們走
Anna, come on.
Anna 快來
We didn't even know they were there.
我們都不知道他們當時在那裡
Dominic and Jesse?
Dominic和Jesse
They must have been waiting for us in the river.
他倆肯定早埋伏在水裡了
Dominic pulled Dan under, and Jesse pulled Jake.
Dominic拽的Dan Jesse拉了Jake
Why?
為何這樣做
It was time to start our families.
我們該成家了
You start your families by killing two innocent victims?
需要殺倆無辜的人才准許嗎
That wasn't supposed to happen.
這種事本不該發生的
In the old days, maybe, but we don't do that anymore.
以前有 但現在沒人這樣做
At least we didn't...
至少我們不會
Till Dominic and Jesse showed up about six months ago.
直到Dominic和Jesse半年前來此
- From where? - Alaska.
- 從哪來的 - 阿拉斯加
Did you know them prior to that?
你們以前認識他們嗎
No. Our relationships are arranged.
不認識 我們是包辦婚姻
Dominic and Jesse come from a family that believe
Dominic和Jesse的家族
in all of these... Old traditions.
信奉這些老傳統
We didn't think that they would actually do anything,
沒想到他們會來真的
we just... we just thought they were talking.
我們以為他倆就是說說罷了
This is some kind of ritual?
這算某種儀式
I think that's what they want us to think,
他們正希望我們這樣想呢
but it's more about revenge.
其實就是報復
We can only conceive and give birth in the water.
我們只能在水下受精 水下分娩
Naiad men are born sterile.
雄性水精生來就是不育的
They know we have to mate with other men.
他們知道我們得和別的男人交配
Otherwise, we'll die out.
否則 我們這個種族就會絕跡
I mean, they're not very happy about it, but neither are we.
他們對此不高興 我們也是啊
Well, I can see where that may cause a little bit of tension.
我能理解 這肯定會有些不快
Our men have to raise the children of other men.
自己的丈夫卻要撫養別人的孩子
I mean, some of them are okay with it, but...
有些人能接受
Others aren't so... Accepting.
但有些人就挺困難的
It's Jake. Hello?
Jake打來的 喂
Detective Burkhardt? It's Jake.
Burkhardt警探 我是Jake
She was just here, the girl who saved me.
那個救我的女孩 剛剛就在這兒
- Where are you? - At my apartment.
- 你們在哪 - 在我公寓
She was in the pool.
她當時在泳池裡
Those two guys from the marina, they jumped me and took her.
從碼頭來的那兩人 把我敲昏 然後把她抓走了
Stay where you are.
你呆在原地
We're gonna send some uniforms your way.
我們派一隊人過去
Jesse and Dominic beat up Jake.
Jesse和Dominic打了Jake
Elly was there, and they took her.
Elly也在那兒 被他們抓走了
Oh, my God, they're gonna cut her.
我的天 他們要割了她
- What? - They'll cut the telae
什麼意思
between her fingers and toes.
把她手指腳趾間的蹼切掉
It's how they used to banish those that broke our laws.
過去常這樣驅逐 那些破壞族規的人
Where would they take her?
他們會帶她去哪兒
- Where they can make an example Home.
能以儆傚尤的地方 家裡
You left us no other choice.
你逼我們這樣做的
I know you can understand me.
我知道你懂唇語
This is for the good of all of us.
這對大家都好
Ugh! Shouldn't have done that!
你會後悔的
Now you're gonna get it!
馬上你就有明白了
Tie her legs.
綁住她的腿
You like their kind so much? Now you can be just like them.
你不是很迷人類嗎 現在你就會和他們一樣了
Ow, damn it! She won't stop kicking.
該死 她老是踢我
I'll make her stop kicking.
我會讓她消停的
Come on, Elly, you gotta breathe sometime.
快 你總要得呼吸的
Breathe.
快喘氣
Stubborn little bitch.
真是倔強哈
Not for much longer. Breathe or drown, Elly!
倔不了多久 你不喘氣就會被淹死
She's breathing.
她喘氣了
- That's a good girl, Elly. - Cut her quick!
- 這才聽話嘛 - 快點切
Damn it! We're gonna have to hold her under again.
該死 還得把她按水裡
- Push her in. - Oh.
把她扔進去
Police!
警察
No, no, you don't!
想都別想
You're staying right here.
你就老實呆這兒
Nick!
Nick
You all right?
你沒事吧
I think so.
應該是的
Are you okay?
你還好吧
I got Dominic and Jesse handcuffed.
Dominic和Jesse被我拷住了
How do you want to deal with them?
他倆要怎麼辦
Lock 'em up.
把他倆關起來
They won't last long.
那他們可撐不了多久
They should've thought about that before.
他倆之前就該有這覺悟了吧
You know how long you were under that water?
你知道你們在水下呆了多久嗎
Thought you were dead.
還以為你們死了
You sure look like it.
你看上去就像掛了一樣
- Oh, my God! Elly? - Elly!
- 天啊 Elly - Elly
- Oh, thank God she's okay. - Oh, baby, come here.
- 謝天謝地 她沒事 - 孩子 過來
You're okay.
你沒事
I'm so sorry.
我真的很抱歉
Oh, my girls.
我的寶貝們
"I can't find anything medically wrong with you,
你身上找不出任何毛病
"except you appear to have a metabolic rate
只有代謝速度似乎
"half a normal person's.
比常人慢半拍
"I can't explain this, but it doesn't seem
這個我沒法解釋
"to be interfering with your life.
但這似乎未影響你的生活
You seem healthy, with tremendous physical endurance."
你很健康 並有超強的耐力
"Bheadr."
"Bheadr"
"Haven't been able to spend the money.
錢還沒花出去
"Royal assassination causing much turmoil.
皇室暗殺案引發了大混亂
"No longer safe. Must leave now.
此地不再安全 迅速離開
Love you, M."
愛你 M
"Love you, M"?
"愛你 M"
Who the hell is M, Nick?
M是誰 Nick
Europe and the world have gathered today
今日歐洲和世界都在關注
in Vienna, Austria, to mourn the passing
奧地利首都維也納 眾人沉痛悼念
of crown prince Eric Renard, second in line
Cronenberg家族王位繼承人
to the Cronenberg throne and empire.
皇室王子Eric Renard的逝世
British media report allegations by an unnamed source
英媒體報道 據某消息來源稱
that an underground movement may have been responsible
一個地下組織
for the crown prince's assassination.
或對刺殺王子一事負責
Austrian police are working with French and British intelligence
奧地利警方與英法情報人員
to find those responsible.
將合力辦案 找出真兇
The question on everyone's mind is
當下 大眾的疑問焦距在
who will be given the reins of this royal family?
皇室的大權 將由誰接管
Number three.
第三個
- You sure? - Yeah.
- 確定嗎 - 對
Look, can I... can I ask you guys something?
我能問你們點事兒嗎
Sure.
當然
I-I'm not so sure how to say this, but...
我不知道該如何表述
You know that girl that pulled me out of the water, Elly?
Elly 把我從水裡救出來的女孩
What about her?
她怎麼了
Well, I don't know,
我也不知道
but I saw something really strange.
但我看見了奇怪的事
- Like what? - Like, I...
怎麼怪
Think she's, like, a mutant or something,
我覺得她是變異人之類的
some kind of, like, mermaid thing... I...
有點像美人魚
Okay, I know how that sounds, believe me.
我知道聽上去像胡話 但相信我
I just... She came over when
她過來時
and she just wasn't... Normal.
反正她就是很特別
Nobody is, Jake.
在波特蘭 人人都不普通
-=伊甸园美剧http://bbs.sfile2012.com=- -=伊甸园字幕站 http://ytet.org=- 荣誉出品 本字幕仅供学习交流 严禁用于商业途径
-------------------------- 本論壇字幕僅翻譯交流學習之用 禁止任何商業用途否則後果自負 --------------------------
-=YTET-伊甸园民间字幕联盟=- 翻译: 校对:Achilles之踵 时间轴:wilson0804@A7
-=YTET-伊甸園民間字幕聯盟=- 翻譯:金萬藏 Hannah 玄武門饞貓小愛 滕秀星 校對:Achilles之踵 時間軸:wilson0804@A7
格林 第三季 第四集完 谢谢观赏
格林 第三季 第四集 完